steelers.com 2019-06-05

# Steelers Privacy Policy | Pittsburgh Steelers - Steelers.com

LAST UPDATED: April 13, 2017

This privacy policy applies to the Steeler's website located at [www.steelers.com](https://www.steelers.com/) (the "Website") as well as to those providing personal information to the Pittsburgh Steelers (collectively, the "Steelers", "we", "our", or "us") via Steeler's mobile applications (the "Applications"), in person at games, at retail locations operated by the Steelers, at special events hosted by the Steelers or on social media sites or on the Steelers Online Store merchandise site (<https://shop.steelers.com/>). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.

  1. Types Of Information That May Be Collected
  2. How Information May Be Collected
  3. How We Use The Information Collected
  4. With Whom The Information May Be Shared
  5. Social Media
  6. Links To Other Websites
  7. Security
  8. Children's Online Privacy
  9. Your Acceptance of the Privacy Policy and Notification of Changes
  10. Correcting/Updating Personal Information
  11. Data Retention
  12. Customer Responsibilities
  13. Your California Privacy Rights
  14. Right to Transfer
  15. Questions About This Privacy Policy

## Types Of Information That May Be Collected

The following are the types of information we may collect:

### Information You Provide Us:

In the course of using the website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number; unique identifiers, such as your username, user password; demographic information, such as your age, gender, education, or ticket holder status; financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information.

### Site Usage Information:

We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your IP address. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

### Email Communications:

When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.

### Preferences:

On our email sign up page (<https://nfl.csharmony.epsilon.com/pc/clubs/steelers/Account/Register>), we ask for preferences, such as favorite player and information you would like to hear about.

## How Information May Be Collected

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

### Registration:

You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

### Steelers Email Alerts:

We offer free Steelers alerts via email to share information with you about the Website, team news, team events, special offers, merchandise, our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the opt out instructions provided at the bottom of any Steelers email.

### Contests or Sweepstakes:

We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes, (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the Website, such as on a winner's page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we do not collect your information and we have no control over the information collected from you. Accordingly, we urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.

### Review and Product Images

The Websites provides its users with the opportunity to comment on articles and products. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose on our Website. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [feedback@fans.steelers.com](mailto:feedback@fans.steelers.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Voting:

Participation is voluntary and results are anonymous. You will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.

### Tracking Technologies:

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by the Steelers and our marketing partners, affiliates, and third party service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use local storage objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to collect and store information.

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the Application, the events that occur within the Application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the Application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the Application.

### IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data:

We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

### Advertising Information:

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Websites or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Geolocation Information:

If you use our Application, we will collect geolocation information to send out special promotions and offers and to verify location for content visibility. You may opt out of location based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at [feedback@fans.steelers.com](mailto:feedback@fans.steelers.com). We will only share this information with our agents for the sole purpose of providing you service requested.

### Transaction Information:

If you conduct a financial transaction with our Website, such as a purchase from our online merchandise store, or signup for Team Pass, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and financial information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. For your protection, such information is collected and stored through encrypted means.

### Paper Forms:

If you provide us with personal information on paper registration forms that information is included in our data base and its use also is subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Information Gathered on Game Days and at Events:

We collect information at events like Steelers Training Camp and around Heinz Field on game days. If you provide us with information in this manner, such information is included in our data base and its use is also subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Sideline Stores:

If we collect information from you at one of our Sideline Stores (either on paper or electronically), such information is included in our data base and its use also is subject to this Privacy Policy.

### Ticket Holders, Etc.:

We collect the email addresses of our Season Ticket Holders, Legends Club members, Suite Holders, Club Seat Holders and those on our ticket waiting list through the Steelers ticket office, both digitally and on paper. Such information is included in our data base and its use also is subject to this Privacy Policy.

## How We Use The Information Collected

As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

  * contact you about the Website;

  * contact you about other websites operated by or on behalf of the Steelers and/or the NFL;

  * contact you relating to your membership status;

  * confirm or fulfill and order you have made;

  * inform you of a prize you have won;

  * monitor or improve the use of the Website;

  * customize the advertising and content you see;

  * monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website;

  * send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive push notifications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

  * send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.

## With Whom The Information May Be Shared:

At times, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes. Steelers will only share personal information with third parties in ways that we described in this Privacy Policy. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:

### Agents:

We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sale of certain itmes from the online merchandise store, handling ticket sales, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

For use of the "Free Steelers Email," your information will be disclosed to Load.com. and all privacy policies within that page apply to all pages for that function. Same is also true when purchasing a print from "PrintRoom.com," all activities on these pages are subject to the privacy policy of each individual site. Please be aware that some of these websites may display the Steelers logos or have the look and feel of www.steelers.com.

### Aggregate Information:

We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

### Other Promotional Offers:

We may send offers to you on behalf of our marketing partners. When we do this, we do not give that partner your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may change your preferences by logging into your account.

### Administrative or Legal Process:

Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights, or protect the rights of other users of the Website.

## Social Media (Features)

Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Links To Other Websites

You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website and onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Websites' logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

## Security

The Website incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

The Steelers maintain practices and procedures designed to keep your information secure and confidential. We use generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use personal information. However, no commercial method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. We restrict and limit access to customer information only to those of our employees or authorized service providers who need it to carry out their business functions for Concordia, and we educate our employees about safeguarding customer information and preventing its unauthorized access, disclosure, or use. We also require each of our authorized service providers who need such information in order to carry out their business functions for us to safeguard against such unauthorized access, disclosure or use.

## Children's Online Privacy

The Website is a general audience website. We do not currently collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. For more information about the privacy practices for our affiliated children's website, please consult the privacy policy at the children's website.

The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's website ([www.the-dma.org](http://www.the-dma.org/)) and explore the Get Cyber Savvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website ([www.getnetwise.org](http://www.getnetwise.org/)) to learn more about parental control tools.

## Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy And Notification Of Changes To The Policy

By using the Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our Website and/or send an email to users who have provided an email address, noting the date of the revision, prior to such change taking effect. Your continued use of the Website after such change constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.

## Correcting/Updating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to access our Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. This can be done by logging into your Steelers Online Store account (<https://secure.steelers.com/Reg/?securejump=1>) or by sending an email to [feedback@fans.steelers.com](mailto:feedback@fans.steelers.com).

## Data Retention

We will retain your information (including geo location data) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [feedback@fans.steelers.com](mailto:feedback@fans.steelers.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Customer Responsibilities

If a feature of the Websites requires a login name and password, you are responsible for the security of your login and passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others. Always remember to logout after your session ends to ensure that other people cannot access your account information.

## Consent to Processing of Information in the United States

Notwithstanding your country of origin, or country, state and/or province of residence, by utilizing our site and/or directly providing personal information to us, you hereby agree to and acknowledge your understanding of the terms of this Privacy Policy, and consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and/or in other jurisdictions as determined by us.

## Opting Out of Receiving Promotional E-mails From the Steelers

If you would no longer like to receive e-mail promotional information or other messages from the Steelers, you may unsubscribe and opt-out of receiving email communications by following the opt out instructions provided at the bottom of any Steelers email.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once per calendar year, information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g. requests made in 2014 will receive information regarding 2013 sharing activities). If you are a California resident and have questions about our compliance with this law, please write to us at CA Privacy Rights (Steelers.com), 3400 South Water Street, Pittsburgh, PA 15203. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. Not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

The Website does not respond to “do not track” requests.

## Right to Transfer

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary set forth in this Privacy Policy, the Steelers reserve the right to disclose and/or transfer your personal information to a third party in connection with a proposed or actual purchase, sale, merger, or any other type of acquisition or financing of all or any portion of the Steelers or any affiliate of the Steelers.

## Questions About This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Website, contact [feedback@fans.steelers.com](mailto:feedback@fans.steelers.com).

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:

3400 South Water Street  
Pittsburgh, PA 15203  
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
